staypoland.com 2019-05-11

# Privacy policy | StayPoland

Etravel S.A. is committed to safeguarding your privacy. Contact us at [rodo@etravel.pl](mailto:rodo@etravel.pl) if you have any questions or problems regarding the use of your Personal Data and we will gladly assist you.

By using this site or/and our services, you consent to the Processing of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.  
This Privacy Policy is a part of our Terms and Conditions; by agreeing to Terms and Conditions you also agree to this Policy. In the event of collision of terms used in Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy, the latter shall prevail.

### Table of Contents

  1. Definitions used in this Policy
  2. Data protection principles we follow
  3. What rights do you have regarding your Personal Data
  4. What Personal Data we gather about you
  5. How we use your Personal Data
  6. Who else has access to your Personal Data
  7. How we secure your data
  8. Information about cookies
  9. Contact information
  10. Credit card data

**Personal Data**  – any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.  
**Processing**  – any operation or set of operations which is performed on Personal Data or on sets of Personal Data.  
**Data subject**  – a natural person whose Personal Data is being Processed.  
**Child** – a natural person under 16 years of age.  
**We/us** (either capitalized or not) – Etravel S.A.

We promise to follow the following data protection principles:

  * Processing is lawful, fair, transparent. Our Processing activities have lawful grounds. We always consider your rights before Processing Personal Data. We will provide you information regarding Processing upon request.
  * Processing is limited to the purpose. Our Processing activities fit the purpose for which Personal Data was gathered.
  * Processing is done with minimal data. We only gather and Process the minimal amount of Personal Data required for any purpose.
  * Processing is limited with a time period. We will not store your personal data for longer than needed.
  * We will do our best to ensure the accuracy of data.
  * We will do our best to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of data.

The Data Subject has the following rights:

  1. Right to information – meaning you have to right to know whether your Personal Data is being processed; what data is gathered, from where it is obtained and why and by whom it is processed.
  2. Right to access – meaning you have the right to access the data collected from/about you. This includes your right to request and obtain a copy of your Personal Data gathered.
  3. Right to rectification – meaning you have the right to request rectification or erasure of your Personal Data that is inaccurate or incomplete.
  4. Right to erasure – meaning in certain circumstances you can request for your Personal Data to be erased from our records.
  5. Right to restrict processing – meaning where certain conditions apply, you have the right to restrict the Processing of your Personal Data.
  6. Right to object to processing – meaning in certain cases you have the right to object to Processing of your Personal Data, for example in the case of direct marketing.
  7. Right to object to automated Processing – meaning you have the right to object to automated Processing, including profiling; and not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated Processing. This right you can exercise whenever there is an outcome of the profiling that produces legal effects concerning or significantly affecting you.
  8. Right to data portability – you have the right to obtain your Personal Data in a machine-readable format or if it is feasible, as a direct transfer from one Processor to another.
  9. Right to lodge a complaint – in the event that we refuse your request under the Rights of Access, we will provide you with a reason as to why. If you are not satisfied with the way your request has been handled please contact us.
  10. Right for the help of supervisory authority – meaning you have the right for the help of a supervisory authority and the right for other legal remedies such as claiming damages.
  11. Right to withdraw consent – you have the right withdraw any given consent for Processing of your Personal Data.

**Information you have provided us with**  
This might be your e-mail address, name, billing address, home address etc – mainly information that is necessary for delivering you a service or to enhance your customer experience with us. We save the information you provide us with in order for you to comment or perform other activities on the website. This information includes, for example, your name and e-mail address.

**Information automatically collected about you**  
This includes information that is automatically stored by cookies and other session tools. For example, your tour request information, your IP address, your request history (if there is any), information on how you use our website, etc. This information is used to improve your customer experience and for analytical purposes. When you use our services or look at the contents of our website, your activities may be logged or tracked.

**Publicly available information**  
We might gather information about you that is publicly available.

We gather and process your Personal Data on legitimate grounds and/or with your Consent in order to:

  * provide our service to you. This includes providing you with services that you have requested; providing you with promotional items at your request and communicating with you in relation to those services; communicating and interacting with you in relation to your orders or requests; and notifying you of changes to any services.
  * provide our business partners with necessary data related to services you ordered. These partners includes hotels, tour guides, and any other third party companies or individuals involved in providing services you ordered.
  * enhance your customer experience;
  *  implementation of marketing and promotional activities. These include sending you offers, newsletters, conducting questionnaires concerning client satisfaction, administering and analysing our client base (purchasing behaviour and history) in order to improve the quality, variety, and availability of services offered; and any other purposes we have asked your consent for
  * fulfil an obligation under law or contract;

We Process your Personal Data in order to fulfil obligation rising from law and/or use your Personal Data for options provided by law. We reserve the right to anonymise Personal Data gathered and to use any such data. We will use data outside the scope of this Policy only when it is anonymised. We save your billing information and other information gathered about you for as long as needed for accounting purposes or other obligations deriving from law, but not longer than 6 years.

We might process your Personal Data for additional purposes that are not mentioned here, but are compatible with the original purpose for which the data was gathered. To do this, we will ensure that:

  * the link between purposes, context and nature of Personal Data is suitable for further Processing;
  * the further Processing would not harm your interests and
  * there would be appropriate safeguard for Processing.

We will inform you of any further Processing and purposes.

We do not share your Personal Data with strangers. Personal Data about you is in some cases provided to our trusted partners in order to either make providing the service to you possible or to enhance your customer experience.

The recipients of personal data, that the Etravel S.A. provides or entrusts, are third parties within the recipient categories such as: travel agents and suppliers, airlines, hotel chains, hotels, car rental companies, railway service providers, shipowners, companies providing personal transport services, insurance companies, reservation system providers, visa brokers, financial institutions involved in payment processing, subsidiaries of the eTravel capital group and other necessary to execute orders.

We only work with Processing partners who are able to ensure adequate level of protection to your Personal Data. We disclose your Personal Data to third parties or public officials when we are legally obliged to do so. We might disclose your Personal Data to third parties if you have consented to it or if there are other legal grounds for it.

We do our best to keep your Personal Data safe.  We use safe protocols for communication and transferring data (such as HTTPS). We use anonymising and pseudonymising where suitable. We monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks.

Even though we try our best we can not guarantee the security of information. However, we promise to notify suitable authorities of data breaches. We will also notify you if there is a threat to your rights or interests. We will do everything we reasonably can to prevent security breaches and to assist authorities should any breaches occur.

If you have an account with us, note that you have to keep your username and password secret.

### Children

We do not intend to collect or knowingly collect information from children. We do not target children with our services.

We use cookies and/or similar technologies to analyse customer behaviour, administer the website, track users’ movements, and to collect information about users. This is done in order to personalise and enhance your experience with us.

A cookie is a tiny text file stored on your computer. Cookies store information that is used to help make sites work. Only we can access the cookies created by our website. You can control your cookies at the browser level. Choosing to disable cookies may hinder your use of certain functions.

**We use cookies for the following purposes:**

  * Necessary cookies – which enable the User to use services available within the Website, for example authenticating cookies used for services requiring authentication within the Website;
  * Functionality cookies – which “remember” settings selected by the User and customize the User’s interface, for example as regards the selected language or the region from which the User comes, size of the font, appearance of the website, etc.
  * Analytics cookies – these cookies are used to track the use and performance of our website and services
  * Advertising cookies – these cookies are used to deliver advertisements that are relevant to you and to your interests. In addition, they are used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. They are usually placed to the website by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. These cookies remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisation.

We use Google Analytics to measure traffic on our website. Google has their own Privacy Policy which you can review [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245). If you’d like to opt out of tracking by Google Analytics, visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

We use HotJar.com tools to track how our customers use the website. Doing so helps us understand the way you use our website and lets us improve it on daily basis. You may opt-out of tracking by HotJar by visiting the following page: <https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out>

We also use third-party vendors cookies (Google, Facebook) for the purpose of displaying personalized advertising content on our site and on other websites (remarketing). The content of ads we display ise based on the history of your visits to our site. For example, if you visit our website and browse the tour catalogue, we may later display you ads with content related to tours pages you visited. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network, or somewhere on Facebook.

You can remove cookies stored in your computer via your browser settings. Alternatively, you can control some 3rd party cookies by using a privacy enhancement platform such as [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), [optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/) or [youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). To opt-out of Facebook remarketing cookie, please visit [www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/](https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen).

For more information about cookies, visit [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

We do not request nor store your credit card data even though a credit card is required to make a reservation with us and are never shared with third parties.

The credit card data are encrypted by 256-bit SSL (secure socket layer) protocol certified by Certum Domain Validation CA SHA2. Thanks to company firewall nobody besides the employee responsible for the payment has any access to customer data.

The credit card details are necessary only to facilitate authorized “mail/phone order” payments for travel services you buy from StayPoland.com and agree to be billed for. You can rest assured that the private date will not be misused.

If you have any questions regarding Processing your Personal Data, your rights regarding your Personal Data or this Privacy Policy, contact our Data Protection Officer: Miroslaw Bohun at [rodo@etravel.pl](mailto:rodo@etravel.pl)

We reserve the right to make change to this Privacy Policy.  
Last modification was made June 05, 2018.
